<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Best Secure Future</string>
    <string name="best_secure_future">Best Secure Future</string>

    <array name="lawsBig">

        <item>According to the International Research Centre for Women, almost 47 percent of girls
            are married before the age of 18. Currently, India ranks 13 in the world when it comes
            to child marriages. Since child marriage has been steeped into the Indian culture and
            tradition since centuries, it has been tough eliminating it.

            The Prohibition of Child Marriage Act was made effective in 2007. This act defines child
            marriage as a marriage where the groom or the bride are underage, that is, the bride is
            under 18 years of age or the boy is younger than 21 years.

            Parents trying to marry underage girls are subject to action under this law. Since the
            law makes these marriages illegal, it acts as a major deterrent.
        </item>

        <item>The objectives of this act is to provide – a special form of marriage in certain
            cases, provide for registration of certain marriages and, to provide for divorce. In a
            country like India and with the diverse religions and cast, when people from different
            faiths and caste chose to get married they do it under the Special Marriage Act.

            It is not applicable to the state of Jammu and Kashmir and also extends to intending
            spouses who are Indian nationals and living abroad.
        </item>
        <item>According to this act, taking or giving of dowry at the time of the marriage to the
            bride or the bridegroom and their family is to be penalised. Dowry system, giving and
            taking of dowry, is a norm in India. Dowry is often asked of the bride and her family by
            the groom and his family. The system has taken strong roots because women after marriage
            move in with their spouse and in-laws. Also, over the centuries, the lack for economic
            independence of women and the taboo towards divorce has resulted in bride burning. When
            demands for dowry even after marriage are not met by the girl’s families, many women are
            tortured, beaten and even burnt.
            It is one of the major challenges that our society is grappling with. Women openly
            complaining about it has helped to spread the word and encourage other women to take a
            stand.
        </item>
        <item>The Indian Divorce Act allows the dissolution of marriage, mutual consent, nullity of
            marriage, judicial separation and restitution of conjugal rights.

            Family Courts are established to file, hear, and dispose of such cases.
        </item>
        <item>This act regulates the employment of women and maternity benefits mandated by law. It
            states that a woman employee who has worked in an organisation for a period of at least
            80 days during the 12 months preceding the date of her expected delivery is entitled to
            receive maternity benefits, which includes maternity leave, nursing breaks, medical
            allowance, etc.
        </item>
        <item>The Act came into effect into 1972, was amended in 1975 and 2002. The aim of the Act
            is to reduce the occurrence of illegal abortion and consequent maternal mortality and
            morbidity.

            It clearly states the conditions under which a pregnancy can be ended or aborted and
            specifies the persons qualified to conduct the same.
        </item>
        <item>To ensure women’s safety at workplace, this Act seeks to protect them from sexual
            harassment at their place of work. Thirty-six percent of Indian companies and 25 percent
            among MNC’s are not complaint with the Sexual Harassment Act according to a FICCI-EY
            November 2015 report.

            Sexual harassment at workplace also includes – the use of language with sexual
            overtones, invasion of private space with a male colleague hovering too close for
            comfort, subtle touches and innuendoes.
        </item>
        <item>This Act prohibits indecent representation of women through advertisement or in
            publications, writings, paintings, figures or in any other manner.
        </item>
        <item>The National Commission for Women (NCW) is a statutory body of the Government of
            India, established in January 1992. Lalitha Kumara mangalam was appointed its
            Chairperson in 2014.

            The NCW represents the rights of women in India and provides a voice for their issues
            and concerns. The National Commission for Women Act aims to improve the status of women
            and worked for their economic empowerment.
        </item>
        <item>This Act prevents discrimination in terms of remuneration. It provides for payment of
            equal recompense to men and women workers.

            It is necessary to know these and other laws in place to protect the interests of women.
            Only if you are aware of your rights can you fight against any injustice meted out to
            you at home, at the workplace, or in the society.
        </item>
    </array>
    <string name="policy">
        App Privacy Policy Generator
Generate a generic Privacy Policy and Terms &amp; Conditions for your apps
Built with heart by Nishant and contributors.

TwitterDisclaimerGitHub stars


While App Privacy Policy Generator is completely FREE, it takes money to keep it running and updated.
If you are able to, then consider contributing by:

Sponsoring me on Github 👨🏻‍💻
Buying me a cup of ☕
If you are unable to contribute with funds, consider sharing it with your friends: Twitter, Linkedin, Facebook, Reddit

…or adding a review/comment in the project\'s GuestBook 🤗

All Done!
Now sit back and choose the type of document you want to generate:




The accuracy of the generated privacy policy and terms &amp; conditions on this website is not legally binding. Use at your own risk.

Read the full Disclaimer here


Terms &amp; Conditions
By downloading or using the app, these terms will automatically apply to you – you should make sure therefore that you read them carefully before using the app. You’re not allowed to copy or modify the app, any part of the app, or our trademarks in any way. You’re not allowed to attempt to extract the source code of the app, and you also shouldn’t try to translate the app into other languages or make derivative versions. The app itself, and all the trademarks, copyright, database rights, and other intellectual property rights related to it, still belong to Incredible India Techexpert.

Incredible India Techexpert is committed to ensuring that the app is as useful and efficient as possible. For that reason, we reserve the right to make changes to the app or to charge for its services, at any time and for any reason. We will never charge you for the app or its services without making it very clear to you exactly what you’re paying for.

The Best Secure Future app stores and processes personal data that you have provided to us, to provide our Service. It’s your responsibility to keep your phone and access to the app secure. We therefore recommend that you do not jailbreak or root your phone, which is the process of removing software restrictions and limitations imposed by the official operating system of your device. It could make your phone vulnerable to malware/viruses/malicious programs, compromise your phone’s security features and it could mean that the Best Secure Future app won’t work properly or at all.

The app does use third-party services that declare their Terms and Conditions.

Link to Terms and Conditions of third-party service providers used by the app

Google Play Services
You should be aware that there are certain things that Incredible India Techexpert will not take responsibility for. Certain functions of the app will require the app to have an active internet connection. The connection can be Wi-Fi or provided by your mobile network provider, but Incredible India Techexpert cannot take responsibility for the app not working at full functionality if you don’t have access to Wi-Fi, and you don’t have any of your data allowance left.

If you’re using the app outside of an area with Wi-Fi, you should remember that the terms of the agreement with your mobile network provider will still apply. As a result, you may be charged by your mobile provider for the cost of data for the duration of the connection while accessing the app, or other third-party charges. In using the app, you’re accepting responsibility for any such charges, including roaming data charges if you use the app outside of your home territory (i.e. region or country) without turning off data roaming. If you are not the bill payer for the device on which you’re using the app, please be aware that we assume that you have received permission from the bill payer for using the app.

Along the same lines, Incredible India Techexpert cannot always take responsibility for the way you use the app i.e. You need to make sure that your device stays charged – if it runs out of battery and you can’t turn it on to avail the Service, Incredible India Techexpert cannot accept responsibility.

With respect to Incredible India Techexpert’s responsibility for your use of the app, when you’re using the app, it’s important to bear in mind that although we endeavor to ensure that it is updated and correct at all times, we do rely on third parties to provide information to us so that we can make it available to you. Incredible India Techexpert accepts no liability for any loss, direct or indirect, you experience as a result of relying wholly on this functionality of the app.

At some point, we may wish to update the app. The app is currently available on Android – the requirements for the system(and for any additional systems we decide to extend the availability of the app to) may change, and you’ll need to download the updates if you want to keep using the app. Incredible India Techexpert does not promise that it will always update the app so that it is relevant to you and/or works with the Android version that you have installed on your device. However, you promise to always accept updates to the application when offered to you, We may also wish to stop providing the app, and may terminate use of it at any time without giving notice of termination to you. Unless we tell you otherwise, upon any termination, (a) the rights and licenses granted to you in these terms will end; (b) you must stop using the app, and (if needed) delete it from your device.

Changes to This Terms and Conditions

We may update our Terms and Conditions from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Terms and Conditions on this page.

These terms and conditions are effective as of 2030-01-17

Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions about our Terms and Conditions, do not hesitate to contact us at anshukumarsingh448@gmail.com.

This Terms and Conditions page was generated by App Privacy Policy Generator
    </string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
</resources>